{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Air Purification \u0026 Cleaner Repair Services","appliedActionRules":{"SDB_SCROLLY_SITE_24719":"SDB_SCROLLY_SITE_24719_ctrl"},"categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40305/":{"taskOID":40305,"originalTaskOID":40305,"setID":605,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":4712,"questionDisplayText":"Air Cleaner Type","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of air cleaner are you using?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2183,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Electrical attraction","answerDisplayText":"Electrical attraction","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2198,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Electrostatic precipitating (\"electronic\")","answerDisplayText":"Electrostatic precipitating (\"electronic\")","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6959,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Whole-house electrostatic precipitating","answerDisplayText":"Whole-house electrostatic precipitating","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2993,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"HEPA air cleaner","answerDisplayText":"Hepa air cleaner","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1409,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Clean air cabinet","answerDisplayText":"Clean air cabinet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":16749,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Don't know","answerDisplayText":"Don't know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4713,"questionDisplayText":"Service Needs","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Why do you need service? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3098,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"House seems dustier","answerDisplayText":"House seems dustier","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2377,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Family member having trouble breathing","answerDisplayText":"Family member having trouble breathing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4715,"questionDisplayText":"Last Time Filter was Cleaned","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"When was the last time the filter was cleaned?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3389,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Just had it cleaned","answerDisplayText":"Just had it cleaned","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4394,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"One-three months ago","answerDisplayText":"One-three months ago","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2615,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Four-six months ago","answerDisplayText":"Four-six months ago","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5753,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Six-12 months ago","answerDisplayText":"Six-12 months ago","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":4712,"questionDisplayText":"Air Cleaner Type","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of air cleaner are you using?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2183,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Electrical attraction","answerDisplayText":"Electrical attraction","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2198,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Electrostatic precipitating (\"electronic\")","answerDisplayText":"Electrostatic precipitating (\"electronic\")","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6959,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Whole-house electrostatic precipitating","answerDisplayText":"Whole-house electrostatic precipitating","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2993,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"HEPA air cleaner","answerDisplayText":"Hepa air cleaner","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1409,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Clean air cabinet","answerDisplayText":"Clean air cabinet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":16749,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Don't know","answerDisplayText":"Don't know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":2183,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Electrical attraction","answerDisplayText":"Electrical attraction","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2198,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Electrostatic precipitating (\"electronic\")","answerDisplayText":"Electrostatic precipitating (\"electronic\")","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6959,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Whole-house electrostatic precipitating","answerDisplayText":"Whole-house electrostatic precipitating","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2993,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"HEPA air cleaner","answerDisplayText":"Hepa air cleaner","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1409,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Clean air cabinet","answerDisplayText":"Clean air cabinet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":16749,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Don't know","answerDisplayText":"Don't know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4713,"questionDisplayText":"Service Needs","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Why do you need service? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3098,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"House seems dustier","answerDisplayText":"House seems dustier","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2377,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Family member having trouble breathing","answerDisplayText":"Family member having trouble breathing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":3098,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"House seems dustier","answerDisplayText":"House seems dustier","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2377,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Family member having trouble breathing","answerDisplayText":"Family member having trouble breathing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4715,"questionDisplayText":"Last Time Filter was Cleaned","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"When was the last time the filter was cleaned?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3389,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Just had it cleaned","answerDisplayText":"Just had it cleaned","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4394,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"One-three months ago","answerDisplayText":"One-three months ago","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2615,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Four-six months ago","answerDisplayText":"Four-six months ago","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5753,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Six-12 months ago","answerDisplayText":"Six-12 months ago","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":3389,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Just had it cleaned","answerDisplayText":"Just had it cleaned","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4394,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"One-three months ago","answerDisplayText":"One-three months ago","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2615,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Four-six months ago","answerDisplayText":"Four-six months ago","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5753,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Six-12 months ago","answerDisplayText":"Six-12 months ago","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","__cache./api/resource/task/40305/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40305,"taskName":"Central Air Cleaner - Repair or Service","taskDescription":"Repair or Service a Central Air Cleaner","xmTaskDescriptor":"Air Purification \u0026 Cleaner Repair Services","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":1714,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Airconditioning ac conditioning units hvac","textMessagingName":"Svc Air Cleaner","rolloverLongDesc":"Typically attached to the main furnace or air conditioner, these devices use static electricity, filters \u0026 other methods to extract impurities from the air. Can help control household dust \u0026 alleviate some problems with allergies.","rolloverShortDesc":"Filters out dust, pollen \u0026 other particles.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Repair or Service a Central Air Cleaner.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Whole House Air Purifier Repair \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Fix Central Air Cleaner","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":39,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Central Air Cleaner Repair","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Central Air Cleaner - Repair or Service","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Central Air Cleaner Project","urlName":"Central-Air-Cleaner-Repair-or-Service","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Central Air Purifier \u0026 Cleaner Repair Pros - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor","searchKeywords":"Airconditioning,ac,conditioning,units,hvac,heating,impurities,extract,systems,cooling,coolers,dust,household,control,airconditioners,filter,system,Cleaner,Central,Air","emcCategoryOid":-12002,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":605,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}